crystalsandjewelry.com 2004-12-04

# CrystalsandJewelry.com Privacy Policy

|   | 

I value your privacy. I've put my privacy policy which is that of my company, Robyn A Harton Creative, out here to show you how I handle it.

This site is a commercial site and as such is not intended for use by children. This site does not automatically collect personally identifiable information from visitors, even if a child does visit. It does collect aggregate, non-personally identifiable information which may be used for marketing or research purposes.

Personally Identifiable Information - Any personally identifiable information must be given voluntarily to me and Robyn A Harton Creative through use of CrystalsandJewelry.com email links or forms, and is held in strict confidence, unless required by law to divulge that information. We do not sell, share, lease or rent any email addresses or other personal information.

Use of Information - Personally identifiable information such as name, email address, phone number, postal address may be used in order to contact individuals regarding purchases, special offers, new items, or other similar legitimate business purposes by Robyn A Harton Creative. Financial information such as credit card numbers or other items are only used to process purchases of services or goods.

Third Party Links - This site has links to third parties. Robyn A Harton Creative cannot be responsible for the privacy policies of any third party sites. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of any third party sites you visit.

Child Protection - Should a child contact Robyn A Harton Creative through this site and inform us that he or she is 13 years of age or younger, we will, as provided by the Child Online Privacy Protection Act, respond to that child once and subsequently destroy all personally identifiable information relating to that child. This is a commercial site and as such we do not have repeated contacts with anyone we know to be under legal age via this site.

If you have questions regarding this site's privacy policy you may contact us at:

Robyn Harton, Owner & Designer  
CrystalsandJewelry.com **  
** Robyn A Harton Creative  
PO Box 413   
Norwich, NY 13815   
USA  
email: [robyn@crystalsandjewelry.com](mailto:robyn@crystalsandjewelry.com)

< **Back**

|   

|    |  | 

Major Credit Cards and PayPal Accepted _ **via Secure Shopping Cart using SSL security to protect your personal shopping information.**_

Robyn A Harton Creative http://CrystalsAndJewelry.com  
Copyright ©2002-2004 Robyn A Harton Creative. All rights reserved.

Disclaimer: **Metaphysical and spiritual healing information is for educational, inspirational, and entertainment purposes only.** Mystical lore on healing and spiritual healing information is not to be construed as prescription, diagnosis or healthcare information. See your Doctor or other healthcare practitioner for all ailments, disease and injury. Robyn A Harton Creative assumes no liability for any use or misuse of this information.

|
